<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<?xml-model href="http://www.tei-c.org/release/xml/tei/custom/schema/relaxng/tei_lite.rng" type="application/xml" schematypens="http://relaxng.org/ns/structure/1.0"?>
<?xml-model href="http://www.tei-c.org/release/xml/tei/custom/schema/relaxng/tei_lite.rng" type="application/xml"
	schematypens="http://purl.oclc.org/dsdl/schematron"?>
<TEI xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
  <teiHeader>
      <fileDesc>
         <titleStmt>
            <title>Letter fom George Bullock to His Sister</title>
         </titleStmt>
         <publicationStmt>
            <p>Personal Letter</p>
         </publicationStmt>
         <sourceDesc>
            <p>Dated Feb 28 1894</p>
         </sourceDesc>
      </fileDesc>
      <encodingDesc>
      <tagsDecl>
        <rendition xml:id="right" scheme="css">display:block;text-align:right;</rendition>
        <rendition xml:id="del-x" scheme="css" >text-decoration:line-through;text-decoration-style:wavy;</rendition><!--This is technically an abuse of the <rendition> element, as this CSS does not actually describe how the striking of this word appears in this document. -->
        <rendition xml:id="del-dbl" scheme="css">text-decoration:line-through;text-decoration-style:double;</rendition>
        <rendition xml:id="ord" scheme="css">vertical-align:super;font-size:70%;text-decoration:underline;</rendition>
        <rendition xml:id="sup" scheme="css">vertical-align:super;</rendition>
      </tagsDecl>
    </encodingDesc>
  </teiHeader>
  <text>
      <body>
         <div type="paragraph">
           <Header>A + M College<lb/>Raleigh, <dateline>Feb 28 1894.</dateline></Header>
             <lb/>
             <lb/>
           <Salute><add>Dear</add> Sister.</Salute>
        </div>
        <div type="page 1">Your letter to me was received Monday the 19th 
                           and I was glad to get it too, it was the first time 
                           your letters were more than a week <choice>
                            <sic>a part</sic>
                            <corr>apart</corr></choice>.
                           I don't believe anything unusual has happened 
                           since I wrote to Lucy the first part of the week. 
                           We did not have any of that snow that you all had, 
                           we had wind and a little snow but did not any stay on
                           the houses even. I don't know whither I to Lucy about how
                           we were going to get a long with one suit of uniform.
                           We wont hvae to wear the uniform all the time and wont
                           have to wear it on Sundays. <lb/>
        </div>
        <lb/>
        <div type="page 2">We will have to get the uniform about the middle of March.
                           One of our Professor has just gotten back from his home
                           where he went to attend his fathers funeral. Col. Holladay
                           has just gotten back from the NEWBORN fair, he said he 
                           would have had a very pleasant time if it had not been such
                           a crowd. Prof. Irby has gone to Statesville to a farmers meeting.
                           Prof. Massey gave us a little talk, as he called it, in the chapel
                           tonight. I think he will also go to Statesville tonight. I have 
                           two jobs for me tomorrow, one is with Mr. Skinner the other is
                           helping Mrs. Holladay _____. I had rather help Mrs. Holladay 
                           to move but as I promised Mr. Skinner to work for <lb/>
        </div>
        <lb/>
        <div type="Page 3">him I reckon I will have to work for him. I debated
                           in my society tonight for first time in I dont know when.
                           I started a letter to Jud last Sunday and ____ it up 
                           before I finished it, and have not finished it yet.
                           I reckon Walter has written you all the news so I will close
                           with love to all I shall ever remain your loving Bro.
        <closer><signed>G. T. Bullock</signed></closer>
        </div>
          
          
          
          
        
         
      </body>
  </text>
</TEI>
